<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>zatunatu</title><description>zatunatu</description><link>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/blog</link><item><title>Rose and Nancy: the story of a timeless friendship</title><description><![CDATA[This is your blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. They can also be a great way to position yourself as an authority in your field. To edit your content, simply click here to open the Blog Manager. From the Blog Manager you can edit posts and also add a brand new post in a breeze.To really engage your site visitors we suggest you blog about subjects that are related to your site or business. Blogging is also really good for SEO, so we recommend<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/0ed0d289218148baaf416dfe1e9f1632.jpg/v1/fill/w_626%2Ch_417/0ed0d289218148baaf416dfe1e9f1632.jpg"/>]]></description><link>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/single-post/2016/05/03/Rose-and-Nancy-the-story-of-a-timeless-friendship-1</link><guid>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/single-post/2016/05/03/Rose-and-Nancy-the-story-of-a-timeless-friendship-1</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 10:23:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>This is your blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. They can also be a great way to position yourself as an authority in your field. To edit your content, simply click here to open the Blog Manager. From the Blog Manager you can edit posts and also add a brand new post in a breeze.</div><div>To really engage your site visitors we suggest you blog about subjects that are related to your site or business. Blogging is also really good for SEO, so we recommend including keywords that relate to your services, products or industry within your posts. It’ll make it easier for people to find you on the web.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/0ed0d289218148baaf416dfe1e9f1632.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Everyone ages: 13 tips to stay youthful</title><description><![CDATA[This is your blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. They can also be a great way to position yourself as an authority in your field. To edit your content, simply click here to open the Blog Manager. From the Blog Manager you can edit posts and also add a brand new post in a breeze. Great looking images make your blog posts more visually compelling for your audience, so choose images that really wow. Adding fun and compelling videos is another<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/2ca0acb2aa424182abef253b318dcdc5.jpg/v1/fill/w_626%2Ch_417/2ca0acb2aa424182abef253b318dcdc5.jpg"/>]]></description><link>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/single-post/2016/05/03/Everyone-ages-13-tips-to-stay-youthful</link><guid>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/single-post/2016/05/03/Everyone-ages-13-tips-to-stay-youthful</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Mar 2018 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>This is your blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. They can also be a great way to position yourself as an authority in your field. To edit your content, simply click here to open the Blog Manager. From the Blog Manager you can edit posts and also add a brand new post in a breeze.</div><div> Great looking images make your blog posts more visually compelling for your audience, so choose images that really wow. Adding fun and compelling videos is another great way to engage your audience and keep them coming back for more. And to organize your posts according to subject-matter, define a ‘Category’ for each post in the Blog Manager.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/2ca0acb2aa424182abef253b318dcdc5.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Maintain healthy relationships throughout your life</title><description><![CDATA[This is your blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. They can also be a great way to position yourself as an authority in your field. To edit your content, simply click here to open the Blog Manager. From the Blog Manager you can edit posts and also add a brand new post in a breeze. To make it easy for visitors to search your blog according to topic, add 'Tags' to your posts in the Blog Manager. You can showcase the very best posts from your blog<img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fd1645f6983c4507a7e8f62bc1bdaa13.jpg/v1/fill/w_626%2Ch_417/fd1645f6983c4507a7e8f62bc1bdaa13.jpg"/>]]></description><link>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/single-post/2016/05/03/Maintain-healthy-relationships-at-any-age</link><guid>https://zatunatu.wixsite.com/website-1/single-post/2016/05/03/Maintain-healthy-relationships-at-any-age</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2018 10:29:00 +0000</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<div><div>This is your blog post. Blogs are a great way to connect with your audience and keep them coming back. They can also be a great way to position yourself as an authority in your field. To edit your content, simply click here to open the Blog Manager. From the Blog Manager you can edit posts and also add a brand new post in a breeze.</div><div> To make it easy for visitors to search your blog according to topic, add 'Tags' to your posts in the Blog Manager. You can showcase the very best posts from your blog by setting a post as a Featured Post. Just click the star icon next to the Post title to define it as a Featured Post. It’s a great, easy way to promote specific content in your blog.</div><img src="http://static.wixstatic.com/media/fd1645f6983c4507a7e8f62bc1bdaa13.jpg"/></div>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>